[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Huh?
My alumna, Shin Bi Gyeong?
Hello, it's 2013.
2013?
Did the rain trigger another time leap?
Huh? Ye Rang...
and Jun Mo!
Bottoms up.
- Let's hand it over to reporter Yoon Ha Na. - Yoon Ha Na?
- Yoon Ha Na? - Reporter Yoon Ha Na...
Did you just call me...
Yoon Ha Na?
It's me!
It's Yoon Ha Na!
But why 2013?
Why not 2026? Why is it 2013?
What's wrong, Ha Na?
You alright, Ha Na?
I'd be 21 in 2013...
So, if he's 21...
Woo Jae must be serving in the army.
- Hey, Yoon Ha Na! - Yoon Ha Na!
Hey, where are you going?
She must be drunk.
Oh, right. Jun Mo.
When are the audition results for the female lead coming out?
It's still under evaluation by the professor.
But soon, I think.
Oh, I see.
Hey, it's not even that promising a script.
What's with the delay, huh?
He's a, uh, he's an odd one, you hear?
Why is this happening?
What went wrong?
[Beast] Why won't he answer?
Oh, my purse!
Thief!
- Move! - It's a thief! A thief!
Move!
- He's a thief! - Out of the way!
You're not going anywhere!
Piss off!
Let go!
Are you alright?
Woo Jae!
- Let go! - Stay down, you scum!
Are you hurt?
- Cheers! - Cheers!
- Enjoy your meal. - Thank you.
- A bottle of soju, please. - A soju, coming right up!
[10:46 PM] [2013/05/31 Friday]
[Yoon's Raw Fish Restaurant]
What are you delaying for? We're busy enough as is!
- Mom! - Seriously!
Hi, Mom...
- What am I doing here? - Oh, my!
You still haven't prepared these?
Really, what have you been doing?
What?
How would I even do this?
I've never done this before!
What are you on about?
You've been hacking off fish heads all day, see that pile?
Come up with a better excuse next time.
Hey, you. Go to Seoul.
I'm taking an hour's worth of wages off of today's shift.
Shift?
What shift?
Am I working part-time here?
You said, once you graduate culinary school,
you'll open a restaurant in Gangnam and make us proud.
Proud, my butt. I'm more concerned about you blowing your tuition.
Restaurant?
Bodyguard?
Yeah.
[Beast]
One moment.
Okay.
What took you so long?
Yoon Ha Ru, where are you right now?
Working part-time at our parents' restaurant.
I'm not a judo player.
I gave up... on judo.
What?
Where are you?
I'm near the campus.
And I'm me, Yoon Ha Na. I'm in my body.
Well, me too.
I'm Yoon Ha Ru, myself.
It's 2013...
I'm in the class of 2012 at Yongwon University, a sophomore in film. You?
I'm studying culinary arts at Yongwon.
I'm a freshman. Class of 2013.
Woo Jae isn't a national player, either.
Security services, Yongwon, class of 2012...
Nothing's going as we expected.
Yeah, no joke.
Let's talk in person.
Yeah, I'll take the first train leaving tomorrow.
Are you done?
Yeah, Ha Ru seems busy.
Of course.
There are always lots of customers at this hour.
- Let's go. - Huh?
Okay...
[2012 National Judo Tournament]
Hey, kiddo.
Kiddo.
Dad?
You trouble-making, naughty, mischievous little bastard...
Can't even bother to stand up at your father's grand arrival?
Are you drunk?
No, I'm not... Hey! Get up!
I... Okay.
Attention.
Don't you dare use your judo skills on me.
Stay still. Arms at your side...
Aw, my cutie-pie little sonny boy...
What's wrong with you?
Oh, you...
My boy.
How's school going?
How's your cooking?
You must be standing up all day in the kitchen.
Are your legs alright?
Yeah, it's fine, I think.
Cooking's not easy, you know...
Hey, I heard they run kitchens like the army. They've got nags and bullies, right?
I say...
if anyone tries to bully you, let me know right away.
I'll go there and take care of stuff!
I'm not a kid anymore!
Dad, this is Yoon Ha Ru we're talking about.
Bullying?
I doubt I'd care.
I mean, I won't!
Stop worrying.
Deary me.
I don't recall you growing up so fast.
I remember when you used to waddle...
and refuse to leave my side like it was yesterday.
And now you're saying you'll become a great cook,
and make us proud.
Not a cook, a chef.
Yeah, yeah.
- Cook. - No, a chef...
Sure.
- Dad. - Yeah?
Remember why I quit judo?
Of course I do.
How would I forget?
They said the surgery went great.
So we all thought you'd make a full recovery and jump straight back into judo...
Oh, boy.
If he keeps competing, he might lose the ability to walk.
I wouldn't recommend that he keep playing judo.
Dad...
My boy...
It's okay.
Cry as much as you want, my boy.
You know, I really...
I'm a man of simple wishes.
I just want you two...
Ha Ru and Ha Na...
to stay healthy, like right now.
All would be well if you two are well.
I, Yoon Chang Sik...
want nothing else in life.
Hey, come on. Pour me a shot.
Okay.
How sweet is that?
How sweet...
When is he coming?
He's taking the first train here tomorrow.
I'll ask him to make me an omelet tomorrow.
An omelet?
From Ha Ru?
Yeah.
Remember? You loved them. Said they were really good.
Oh, yeah.
Yoon Ha Ru... sure makes a great omelet.
After Ha Ru injured his knee...
and me, my shoulder, and we both quit judo...
Everyone was worried about the two idiots who knew nothing other than judo.
But we both seem to have found our paths, no?
Yeah.
I guess so.
Yoon Ha Ru has always been passionate about food.
Your father's a great cook, too.
Maybe that's why,
but he's clearly talented at cooking.
I really do think he'd become a great chef.
Where are we going?
Home.
Home?
Your home?
Our... home.
Our home?
Yeah.
Right there.
[Happy Home]
Wait, this is...
the sharehouse that I lived in as a student!
Aren't you coming in?
Yeah, I'm going in.
[Happy Home]
[Happy Home - Vacancy Available immediately!]
It's just the same!
This place hasn't changed a bit, just as I remember.
[Jung Woo Jae] [Yoon Ha Na]
She's acting a little strange today.
Ha Na.
Mind if I shower first?
Oh, go ahead.
What happened here?
What is this?
Am I...
Am I living with Woo Jae?
[That Day's Warmth] [World-famous star actress Yoon Ha Na]
That's cringe!
Wait a minute.
If that's the case...
This used to be Ha Ru's room...
but now it's Woo Jae's, huh?
Sorry, sorry.
I just need to check something. Just a moment will do.
[Etiquette for the toilet]
[Practical Theory of Security Services]
Why...
Why did it have to be security services?
[6:00 AM - Wake up 6:30 AM - Breakfast...]
Well, something's changed, at least.
So that's why you joined the army back then.
Because of your father's debt.
Sure, it's a shame he's not in the national team,
but this isn't half bad.
I don't like that he's going to become a bodyguard,
but he's only 21.
There's plenty of time to change things.
I can do this...
Ha Na? What are you doing?
Oh, I was...
looking for my cup.
I thought you might've used it.
But it's not here.
Check in Yoon Ha Ru's room.
Yeah, Yoon Ha Ru.
Never puts things back in place... yeah.
Are you hungry?
No!
Well, I could go for something.
Want some ramyeon?
Oh, yeah. If you want to.
How about a beer to go with it?
Sure.
You're being so weird today, Ha Na.
Oh, I'm just... happy.
- About what? - Us.
- Huh? - What?
I mean, us,
and this beer,
and this ramyeon...
This night, just good vibes, you know?
You get me, don't you?
I, well...
Yeah, I guess.
Anyway...
Why do you want to become a bodyguard?
I just...
I have someone I want to protect.
Let me go!
What's this?
Oh, Bi Gyeong!
- And Soo Hyuk, too... - Yeah, hi.
How did the after-party go?
She's really drunk.
Cute.
I mean, she's so drunk she'll have to crawl upstairs.
Yoon Ha Na.
You left the party so early...
and you're with Jung Woo Jae?
Bi Gyeong, you must be tired.
You must be exhausted, too, Ha Na.
Should we wrap this up and call it a night?
- Oh, yeah. - Good.
Here, have a sip.
Do you want to go upstairs? I can...
Don't touch me!
S-sorry.
There we go.
Let's go.
Departing now!
Stop!
You little punks... You go to sleep on time, you hear?
I'll give you a proper scolding...
- Yeah, sure... - Go!
Good night. Soo Hyuk, you did well.
Yeah, good night!
Go!
- I'll clean up. - Okay.
I have someone I want to protect.
Woo Jae, your form has greatly improved since last year.
You'd do great in practice.
Thank you, sir.
Let's have dinner sometime soon.
Yes, sir.
Next team!
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
[Creating a role] Now...
The first thing that an actor should look for...
is the character's dream.
Something that burns hot in their chest.
Also called a super-objective.
An actor is someone who dives into a character's life,
and rewrites their fate.
If one loves the role more than anyone else,
- they, by themselves... - Going to the past isn't what swaps our bodies,
but we swap each time we time travel.
Which means, if we go back to the present now,
I'll be Yoon Ha Ru again!
[2026: Present]
Come to think of it, we've only returned to the present once.
We're not stuck like this, lost in the past, are we?
[Time travel: body change] We've been jumping so much.
So why can't I figure out the pattern?
So handsome!
- Look at his nose! So sharp! - Unreal.
Did you see that?
- This can't be real. - So good-looking!
How does he do it?
He goes to our school?
- So handsome! - Who is that?
No way he goes to our school.
He's so handsome!
He's just my type!
- He's glowing! - Oh, what do I do?
Just as I expected...
The judo player Yoon Ha Ru may be lost in time,
but my charming presence overthrows the fabric of time and space.
Grab him.
Who's that?
Hey.
Time's up. Why are you still here?
Wait, then.
Our national player is still wrapping up.
So, what's he doing?
It looks to me like he's sleeping.
It's the rule to clear out five minutes before practice.
We need to practice.
So clear out. Now.
What do you even practice with?
Do you play tag or something?
What did you say? Say it again.
Hey!
What's all this noise about?
Stick to the rules.
Oh, my bad.
Guess all the judo dropouts like to huddle up in security services.
You little...
Are your classes treating you well?
Yeah.
I see.
That's good to hear.
Aren't you leaving?
I am.
Don't fret.
Guys! Let's move!
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
Wow, what a joke.
Are we just going to let them be?
You'd beat him in 3 seconds tops!
It's fine.
Let's just get ready for practice.
- Hey, you. Come here! - Let's not, okay?
Let me at them. Hey!
That's it for today.
See you next class.
- Yes, ma'am! - Good work, everyone!
Do you want to go eat something?
- Yeah, let's go. - Yeah!
Guys, wait just a second!
Just a moment.
The casting results for the short film are here.
We've confirmed with the professor.
We'll start with the female lead.
The short film competition in 2013...
The female lead, So Hee, goes to...
Yoon Ha Na.
Of course, the female lead is Yoon Ha Na.
Your face has such good coherence.
As for the lens...
A '60s Carl Zeiss. That would do nicely.
- Congrats. - Haesol's pride!
Haesol's princess, Yoon Ha Na!
- Thank you. - You need to be the sturdy centerpiece.
- Got it? - Yes!
The female lead, So Hee, goes to...
Please, please...
Yoon Ha Na.
Of course the female lead is Yoon Ha Na.
Your face has such good coherence.
As for the lens...
A '60s Carl Zeiss. That would do nicely.
Wow.
Look at Ha Na.
Not even a blink, huh?
- Congrats. - Congratulations, Ha Na!
Haesol's pride, Haesol's princess, Yoon Ha Na!
You need to be the sturdy centerpiece, got it?
The professor said that you're the one for this role.
Oh, of course.
This film won four awards at the Busan International Film Festival.
Jun Mo won Best New Director at the Grand Bell Awards,
and I won Best New Female Lead.
It was invited to overseas film festivals and gained a lot of traction, too.
Thank you, Jun Mo.
Your persona, Yoon Ha Na's life... is back in motion.
As for the male lead...
it's yet to be announced.
As you all know,
this role doesn't talk a lot but instead puts weight on action scenes.
Which is why I think...
maybe we should widen our search.
Get applicants from other departments, too.
I remember a complete amateur phys. ed student ended up as the male lead.
Wait.
What if Woo Jae wasn't a bodyguard, but an actor?
What if he wasn't the protector,
but became someone who gets protected?
Physically adept, action-ready,
and a dramatic look in the eyes, you get me?
- Ha Na? Anything to add? - Jun Mo!
Physically adept, action-ready, and a dramatic look in the eyes, right?
Yoon Ha Na...
That's what I was about to say. Did you just read my mind?
You're creeping me out!
A tall-as-a-door male lead with a whole story to tell with his back, right?
I guess... I understand what half of that means.
What do you mean, "tall-as-a-door?"
Like, someone with an overwhelming physical presence,
and is a heartthrob at the same time and tall...
is what they call... people like that.
I think.
Who says that?
I guess it's one of those trendy new words.
- Like, "hot stuff" or "ripped chad." - Yeah.
Something like that, probably.
What are you all amazed about?
Kids these days with their nonsense words!
Say, "he's well-built,"
"he's strong and handsome,"
or "he's built like a warrior."
See all these perfectly good ways to describe someone?
It's just all too much...
It's a bit much. Right, Jun Mo?
I agree.
That's the kind of male lead I want.
"Tall-as-a-door!"
- Okay. - Yeah, okay.
Hey, Ha Na.
Can we leave, too?
[Yoon Ha Na] I'm here. Come out.
Seo Ye Rang?
I lost again...
Why can't I win just once?
I stayed up all night practicing a thousand times, so why...
Why can't Seo Ye Rang win against Yoon Ha Na?
Wow, she's always been this mad.
Everyone's lying when they say working hard is also a talent.
It's honestly a curse!
Just futile hope.
Don't cry, Seo Ye Rang.
Keep your head up high, Seo Ye Rang.
She's crying?
Seo Ye Rang is crying?
Why are you crying?
Oh, it's you, Yoon Ha Ru...
I don't know...
I want to be good, too...
Oh, this is the moment!
- This is when I first met her. - I hate everything!
Who did it? Who did this to you?
- What the hell? - Who did this?
Which bastard was it? Just say the word!
I'll take care of...
I'll do things! Yeah!
Excuse me...
What are you doing?
What?
Wait, something's wrong.
Why aren't you cuddling up to me?
What?
Did you really just ask me... why I'm not cuddling you?
What am I supposed to think of this borderline-innovative-loon?
You're just so cute, Seo Ye Rang.
What?
How do you know my name? I've never seen you before.
Who the heck are you?
Babe, it's me...
It's Yoon Ha Ru, whom you had a debilitating crush on back then.
Are you a student here?
Class of 2013, culinary arts.
- How old? - 30...
I mean, 21.
You rude little thing, how dare you talk to me like that?
I guess you've always been aggressive, babe...
You!
I'll let you off easy this time, because I feel sorry for your delusional head,
but if I ever cross paths with you again,
I'll show you what true aggression is.
So you'd better watch where you're going.
Ugh, I should just...
I'm pissed off already, I can't deal with this.
Why?
Why hasn't she fallen in love with me?
But I look good today!
Why?
- Hi. - Gosh, you scared me!
There you are.
Look who's grumpy.
You're so ugly when you frown.
I'm sorry, Yoon Ha Ru.
This is all my fault.
If only I didn't get you injured...
Oh, you're moping again.
Hey, if I'm being honest, I've had my fair share of judo.
No, not even that. I was getting sick of it.
From primary school up until I reached 33, that's a long 22 years.
I've won every color of every medal.
And I already made my way to the top. Global ranking number one.
What makes you think I have unfinished business with my judo journey?
I would've had my pants in a knot anyway after retiring.
Honestly, this is better.
Yoon Ha Ru, who's already had the world under his thumb, still 21?
I've got so much potential. Yes, I do!
But...
You know what I always think?
You have a tendency to... underestimate me.
You think less of me, don't you?
When did I do that?
If Yoon Ha Ru made a choice at 20 years old,
he must've had a good reason.
I trust in him.
That's why I'll support his choice.
You should trust in me, too, and support me!
So what's that reason of yours?
That's, well...
That's for us to find out.
You'll muck up your luck if you keep making that face.
So, what should we do with Jung Woo Jae?
What's his deal? Was he your guard dog in a past life?
Why is he so dead set on protecting you?
Is that his life's calling, or what?
Speaking of...
Why are you all serious now? You're freaking me out.
I'm going to make Woo Jae an actor.
- An actor? - Yeah.
Does he want to?
We'll make him!
- We? - Well...
You don't have to help.
It's not like you to back down like that.
We can try and make it work. Why not?
Really?
He's my friend, too, you know.
- Such a manly body... - But he's got a baby face!
- As cool as a breeze... - But as hot as the sun!
I can't believe you're real...
I'm going to become a fan.
This is you, right?
I guess that's me, but... What's this about?
Nice to meet you!
We saw this and we instantly knew it.
Knew what?
You already belong to the public.
It's time for the whole country to fall in love with you!
Absolute heartthrob.
You're the most handsome guy I've ever seen.
You're so, so, so cool!
Which is why we made this.
Ta-da!
[We will protect Jung Woo Jae!] Our day one has already started!
- What? - We, the Woo Jae Guardians, will protect you!
I have to get to practice, so if you'll excuse me...
- Oh, yeah, of course! - Right, uh, please, take this.
Right, thank you.
He's popular.
Yeah, no joke.
He's... very popular.
- Bye! - Hey, we're leaving.
Hey, Woo Jae. Hear that? You're "public domain."
Stop teasing me. They're just poking fun.
Doesn't seem that way to me.
The "Woo Jae Guardians?"
Well, I'm convinced.
The whole country will fall in love with you.
Cut it out, Yoon Ha Ru.
I still have another session.
See you at home.
- Okay, good luck at practice! - Thanks.
Oh, you want this?
Yes.
I'll be going, then.
- Bye! - See you!
Bye!
- We love you! - Goodbye!
Love you!
- Bye! - Take care!
- Is that his girlfriend? - That was unreal!
He's so tall!
- I think I've fallen for him again! - So handsome!
That's not how love works.
Hey, you can have this.
Okay...
Those little brats, they're basically children!
I'd like for that to happen to me...
What's with their heights, too?
You sure you'll be alright?
What do you mean?
Just one video online, and now he's got a fan club.
Once he becomes an actor,
there'll be a line of girls wanting to get with him.
Would you be able to deal with that?
What're you yapping for?
Hey, I'm Yoon Ha Na.
Crowned Best Actress at Baekryong, every Gen Z's wannabe role model!
The icon of sold-out tickets, the undefeated "most datable celeb," Yoon Ha Na!
Got it?
It doesn't bother me one bit.
I see that only four measly "Woo Jae Guardians" have completely broken you.
Your face is a sight to see.
Shut it.
So, you've seen it now. He's got potential.
I can feel that something's brewing.
I don't think we should let this opportunity pass us by.
And opportunities are best when seized.
A bit of skill and a lot of luck go a long way.
It's all about the right timing. This time...
He won't have anyone's back, but instead, he'll be standing up front.
Alright. So, what's next?
So you have a plan!
Let me hear it, too!
Come on, just a hint!
Hey, try it out.
["That Summer, Us" Male Lead Audition] Sounds like fun.
Wait, the class of 2008 is Yang Jun Mo's class!
- Let's go. - Okay.
["That Summer, Us" Male Lead Audition]
[Any student at Yongwon University may apply. No prior acting experience needed.]
Don't give it away, okay? Act natural.
He's quick to pick up on things, you know.
Would you stop worrying? Just trust me.
People suggested that I become a child actor when I was little and stuff.
- Shut up. - I swear!
Oh! What is this?
Glad you asked!
It's a short film that I'm going to be in.
But we don't have a good male lead, so there's going to be an audition.
Really?
This could be the path to fame!
Maybe I should give it a shot?
You could!
Anyone can apply! It's a free audition.
An audition?
I see!
Jung Woo Jae, why don't you give it a shot?
Me?
No way, I can't do that.
Why not? Physically adept, action-ready, and a dramatic look in the eyes. That's you!
That's you!
Oh, no.
An overwhelming physical presence, who's also a heartthrob!
There's no denying it, you fit the bill!
You!
A heartthrob?
Me?
I mean...
The Woo Jae Guardians, they seemed to think that.
Ba-dump, ba-dump.
Pit-a-pat.
No way.
I don't know how to act.
This is all because your acting sucked!
What? I thought I did amazing!
Woo Jae, the male lead role's name is Gang Ho.
"Gang Ho," because he's such a gangster, and hot!
Please, just read the script! Just once!
The male lead role's name is Gang Ho.
"Gang Ho," because he's such a gangster, and hot!
Please, just read the script, just once!
- Ha Na... - Woo Jae.
Life is a drama, and you're the main actor.
Let's quit being Woo Jae the bodyguard,
and write an awesome fantasy with me!
You'll be Jung Woo Jae, a worldwide star!
But Ha Na...
My life is more like a documentary.
Not a fantasy.
See you at home. Bye.
Your face is already a fantasy!
You should be charged guilty for not putting your looks to use!
Yoon Ha Na! Hi!
How's your movie going?
Oh, the movie...
I don't know, it might get scrapped because a certain someone won't play the male lead.
Oh, my!
What a disaster, oh, no!
Oh, these awesome lines and beautiful scenes...
I really hoped to let the world see this...
How I wish upon the stars for someone to play the male lead!
- Ha Na. - Yeah? Why? You'll do it?
No, well...
You're holding the script upside down.
Whatever.
I'll apply for the audition, but that's it.
Really?
You promise, Woo Jae? You'll do it?
Don't get your hopes up.
- I won't make it. - Oh, yeah!
I mean, you'll make it!
Do you want to see the script?
Good, now turn the light up.
Straighten that banner out!
[That Summer, Us]
Is that good? More.
To the right!
That's good!
Okay, that's good.
["That Summer, Us" Male Lead Audition]
Kim Jun Woo, physical education, class of 2013.
- Here. - This way. Follow me.
Hello, everyone! This is Kim Jun Woo, class of 2013!
Hello! I'm Gang Li Ho, class of 2013!
I'll demonstrate my shadowboxing skills!
Hi, everyone! I'm Kim Seong Hoon, class of 2013!
I'll be singing a song today!
♪ Our paths may diverge time and time again ♪
♪ But I'll still wait for you ♪
♪ My heart may break beyond repair ♪
♪ But I'll still smile for you ♪
♪ I may turn away... ♪
I'm sorry.
I don't think this is working at all.
Get him out of here.
Greetings, everyone!
I'm Han Soo Hyuk, the film department's cutie-patootie, class of 2013!
Gang Ho will be mine!
Today, I'll act out getting shot!
In the middle of a war...
Oh, Mother...
Mother... I feel something hot on my belly...
Oh, boy.
Jung Woo Jae is here.
Just go over there.
Let's see him in action first.
Yes, sir.
Imagine that he's a threat to the female lead.
- Let's see you take him down. - Alright.
What in the world?
He's an absolute paragon!
The cream of the crop!
That's Gang Ho, for sure.
Yoon Ha Na, and that guy...
Their facial structures just complement each other perfectly!
I can see them lined up for the ultimate optimal shot!
Could you do that once more?
Sure.
Let's see how you look on camera.
Imagine there's someone whom you'd give your life to protect...
standing in front of the camera, and look into it.
Ready, action!
Cut.
Have you ever acted before?
No, not at all.
That's fine. We can make do.
I can't believe this!
The national judo player, Lee Hyeong Won...
he wants to take the audition!
- Oh, my god! - What? Lee Hyeong Won?
Yeah, Lee Hyeong Won!
Right this way.
Hi, Yoon Ha Na.
I heard you're the female lead.
Yeah, I am.
I'll play it. Your counterpart.
Lee Hyeong Won literally wants to act in our film.
This is a great opportunity!
What are we even on the fence about?
We're guaranteed to go viral if it gets on social media!
What do you think, Ha Na?
It's your counterpart, after all.
I still think that Jung Woo Jae explained the character,
and his acting was way better than Lee Hyeong Won.
The director will do the explaining,
and we can teach him to act.
But you need to be born with that star quality.
Wouldn't you agree, Director Yang?
But still, we shouldn't decide based on what would go viral.
I think Jung Woo Jae's acting was superb.
I honestly couldn't believe he's an amateur. Gave me goosebumps.
Don't you think so, Jun Mo?
I think that... Mr. Jung Woo Jae?
His actions and acting had that deeply touching element to it.
"Mr. Jung Woo Jae?" Really?
You rat.
This is what's wrong with our society, everything's based on connections.
I know you were in the same judo team as him in high school.
Is that why you're siding with him?
- No. - "No?"
You think you're cheeky, huh? Yeah, you've got some cheek right here.
Going viral is what makes a film successful.
With Lee Hyeong Won's name value added, this film will go places, I assure you!
Well, optically speaking...
Yoon Ha Na and Jung Woo Jae would make the most visually satisfying pair.
So, you prefer Jung Woo Jae?
Yeah, but even if we decided on Lee Hyeong Won,
I could work my magic with the '62 vintage Zeiss...
There's no need to worry.
I've made up my mind.
- Lee Hyeong Won. - Yes!
And Jung Woo Jae.
The two will have another audition.
That Lee Hyeong Won, or whatever, took Woo Jae's place in the national team,
and he wants to meddle with his life again?
Jung Woo Jae.
I'll train you myself, the best actress of the year.
[That Summer, Us]
I'll play it.
Your counterpart.
A callback audition, huh?
[Gang Ho approaches So Hee and holds her hand tight, as if he'd never let go]
Holding hands is just holding hands.
What's with all these "tightly" shenanigans?
[Gang Ho embraces So Hee and pats her back. The two are pressed up against each other]
"Press up against each other?" What? Why?
What's wrong with this director guy anyway?
Yang Jun Mo? You...
[A long, deep, intimate kiss to confirm their love]
"K-kiss?"
"A long kiss?"
How long?
Oh, no.
That means Ha Na might have to shoot this with that bastard, Lee Hyeong Won...
A deep kiss?
Not a peck, a real kiss...
A kiss...
Not smooching, a kiss...
Should I just beg her not to do it?
Woo Jae, are you busy?
Just a moment.
Tightly held hands?
Pressing up against each other? A long kiss?
Let's do this.
Okay...
[Scene 1. A lone bus stop, daytime]
[Gang Ho says his last goodbye to So Hee]
I wish you the best.
[So Hee, however...] I'll be going now.
[grabs Gang Ho's hand.]
Don't go.
[Scene 4. The bus stop, daytime]
[So Hee cries tears of relief in Gang Ho's arms]
[Gang Ho embraces her and pats her shoulder]
You need to pat my back.
[Scene 6. Road leading out of town, daytime]
[The two look at each other]
[Gang Ho hugs So Hee, and whispers in her ear]
I promise.
I'll never leave you all alone.
Ha Na, you're great at acting.
Yeah...
Got a grasp on what emotions you should be conveying?
Yeah, I get it too well.
I was actually wondering...
Do you do everything that the script says?
Yeah, that's how it works.
Is that so?
Well, most of the time, we follow the script as is.
But sometimes, we add in more spice on the set.
What?
Or sometimes, we water it down, too.
Oh, okay.
Are you angry?
Angry?
What? No, I'm not.
Lee Hyeong Won...
must be practicing, too, right?
Why?
Does it bother you?
Let's be honest. He's at an advantage.
He's famous, you know.
Jung Woo Jae.
Don't be scared.
The way I see it, you should play Gang Ho.
You're Gang Ho himself.
So, believe in yourself.
Me?
But he and I are both amateurs anyway.
If we're similar in skill, of course they'd pick the celebrity.
Similar? No, he's not even close!
Besides, you have something that he doesn't.
What?
Jung Woo Jae's very own personal coach, Yoon Ha Na!
Yeah, you're right.
If you can't put faith in yourself,
put faith in me, who believes in you.
Got it?
Okay.
In the script,
everyone calls So Hee "misfortune."
Everyone around her ends up miserable.
But letting that fear of the future get a hold of you,
and leaving someone you love because of it?
I think that's what's most unfortunate.
So I do understand Gang Ho, to a degree.
I think we have a lot in common.
What do you think he'd be like?
I think he's someone who always keeps a promise.
Even when the whole world changes and turns its back,
he'd remember his promise to So Hee and stay by her side.
That's who he is.
A promise...
I'll confess to you again, properly...
after the trials.
When I make the national team,
and you get admitted to your dream college...
we'll talk again.
Hey, Ha Na.
Yeah?
I...
I have something I need to tell you.
I wanted to say it sooner...
But...
I injured myself after I made the team,
and then got busy applying for college...
and you got into your dream college.
And...
I... I mean...
When I make the national team,
and you get admitted to your dream college...
we'll talk again.
I...
really like you.
I really mean it.
I like you a lot.
Ha Na.
What's going on here?
He keeps trying to take over Woo Jae's place.
Why is he so tangled up in our business?
No way.
I. Yoon Ha Na, 34 years old...
Ha Na!
- He's so confident! - Give me your number!
Is your heart beating yet?
I don't care what you do to me. But...
I won't let you hurt Ha Na.
Hey. What's this?
There's no need to be afraid.
I'll protect you, no matter what.
No!